In this lesson, we'll review how to access the example projects from oppressive via the API reference
and via GitHub.
Also, we'll use the SPF eclipse to access and build and flash an example from the SPF.
OK, so if you're new to using the SPF 30 two and or the SPF, the example projects can help you get
started as they demonstrate features and provide code that you can adapt for your own projects.
OK, so I'm standing on the programming side now, and I'll just head over to the API reference.
And this is the complete list.
And later, we'll go through the API reference of various features relevant to the application, we're
developing the API reference often or perhaps always includes links to ESP IDF examples.
For example, if we go over to Ethernet.
We see that code examples for the Ethernet API are provided in the Ethernet directory of the Aespa RDF
examples.
So let's follow that.
And here are the Ethernet examples, and the read me with details.
This is a depressives GitHub for the Aespa PDF.
And if you open the link in the resources that I've provided called expressive ESP, IDF GitHub.
Which is here you'll find the full list of example projects.
OK, so another convenient way to access the examples is directly from the SPF eclipse, you have created
a separate workspace just to demonstrate how to access the examples so you don't have to do what I'm
doing now.
So first, I'll close this welcome tab.
And then I'll go to file.
New.
Oppressive IDF project.
And then I'll give it a name.
And then click next.
And I'll just maximize this so you can see it better.
And then if I check this box, create a project using one of the templates, we can access the examples
directly and create the project in Eclipse.
So all the examples are here, including peripherals.
But I'll just load the Blink project swell, select it, then click Finish.
And first, update, the target to ESP 30 to.
And then I'll select the serial port.
From my rover dev kit.
So I'll just expand the project files.
And I'll open the blinkered see.
An update, the Blink GPIO to one of the LEDs on my death kit.
And then I'll build the project.
And we want to build now so that we can generate the SDK config file so that we can make the change
regarding the certificate.
OK, so now the SDK config is generated.
So now let's do the update regarding the certificate.
And we'll say use only the most common certificate.
And then now we can rebuild.
OK, so now I'll flash the example.
And now I can see that the red lady on my death kit is blinking based on the interval from the example.
All right, and also, we can open a monitor to view the print messages.
And we see the lead turning off and then turning on over and over based on the interval.
All right.
So there you have it.
So that's all for now and see you in the next one.